## Semanur Çelebi, Frontend Developer

Rotterdam, Netherlands, 0627907104, semanur.celebi@outlook.com

	Rotterdam, Netherlands, 062/90/	104, semanur.celebi@outlook.com	
LINKS	Linkedin, Github, Portfolio		
PROFILE	Developed my skills as a Front-End Developer at an e-commerce website, gaining valuable experience with Vuc and JavaScript over the past 2 years. Actively participated in updating older projects to new technologies and successfully translated design concepts into functional code. Contributed to improving the user experience b providing my comments on the design of some projects. Outside of work, Organize weekly board game night honing my strategic thinking and collaboration abilities.		
EMPLOYMENT HISTORY			
Dec 2023 — Present	Freelance Frontend Developer	, Tellpal	Rotterdam, Netherlands
	<ul> <li>Tellpal is an application where children can listen to stories through a mobile app.</li> </ul>		
	<ul> <li>Created a website based on the provided designs to promote the application, resulting in an increase of u to 20% in the download rate of the app.</li> </ul>		
	• Additionally, I supported the creation of a user-friendly website by sharing my experiences in design.		
Jan 2022 — Jul 2023	Frontend Developer, Beymen	Group	İstanbul, Turkey
	<ul> <li>Created from scratch an employee performance evaluation project in the Beymen Group to improve operational efficiency.</li> </ul>		
	<ul> <li>With this project, the performances of almost 50 developers working in the company began to be monitored through the website instead of Excel.</li> </ul>		
	<ul> <li>Played a key role in the development of the Beymen e-commerce website, focusing on improvements in th cart, order, and payment functionalities, which resulted in a 15% increase in overall checkout completion rates in one year.</li> </ul>		
	<ul> <li>Migrated the given designs to the project using Figma and Zeplin.</li> </ul>		
	<ul> <li>Took part in migrating projects written with Jquery to Vue2.</li> </ul>		
	Reviewed code, debugged problems and corrected issues.		
	Estimated work hours and tracked progress using Scrum methodology.		
Jul 2021 — Dec 2021	Software Engineer Intern, Onftech Software Solutions İstanbul, Turke		
	<ul> <li>Contributed to a Human Resources project developed from scratch using React and TypeScript, resulting in a 10% decrease in processing time for HR tasks.</li> <li>Written backend code in C# and prepared SQL queries as needed.</li> </ul>		
EDUCATION			
Sep 2017 — Mar 2022	Software Engineering, Karade	niz Technical University	Trabzon, Turkey
SKILLS	Vue	Figma & Zeplin	
	React	Tailwind	
	JavaScript	Git	
	TypeScript	Jira	
	RestAPI	Scrum	
	HTML & CSS		
PASSIONS	Board Game		
	Volleyball		
	Reading - Mainly Detective		
	Anime		

Traveling